https://www.msitec.com/terms-and-conditions/

ROBOTICS
Robotics Manufacturers
Denso RoboticsOmron AdeptPiabRobotiqUniversal RobotsYaskawa Motoman Industrial RobotsZimmer
Robotics Products
4-Axis SCARA Robots5- and 6-Axis RobotsCartesian RobotsCollaborative RobotsEnd of Arm ToolingMobile RoboticsUR Robot Pedestal
FEATURING: Universal Robots New e-Series > LEARN MORE
SERVICES & SOLUTIONS
Automation & Motion Control ServicesIndustrial NetworkingIndustrial ComputingRobotics Services & SolutionsSubassemblies
Industries
AutomotiveFactory AutomationFood and BeverageIntelligent TransportationMedicalPackagingPower GenerationRenewable EnergySemiconductor
CONTACT US
Contact Us FormRequest a QuoteRMA RequestRequest LiteratureGeneral Terms
SEARCH
Search for:
Search
Search
Search for:
Search
MSI TEC Automation, Motion Control, Industrial Networking & Computing, Robotics, Machine Intelligence
Skip to content
MENUMENUAUTOMATION & MOTION CONTROL
Automation Manufacturers
AdvantechAllmotion (CA Only)APEXCGICopley Controls (CA Only)GalilIndusoftLintechMoog-AnimaticsMoxaNSKOmron AutomationOriental MotorR+WRFIDSchneider/IMSSTITHKThomson BSA (CA Only)UnitronicsWeidmullerYaskawa
Automation Products
Automation ComponentsMotors and DrivesPrecision MechanicsPneumaticsProgrammable Logic ControllersSensing and Safety
INDUSTRIAL NETWORKING & COMPUTING
Networking Manufacturers
AdvantechAxiomtekEwonIndusoftMoxaMicrohardProxim
Networking Products
Ethernet SwitchesConnectivityProtocol GatewaysSecure RoutersIIOT GatewaysRemote Access
Remote Monitoring
Industrial ComputersSerial ConvertersWireless Networks
FEATURING: Moxa Custom Quick Ship Industrial Computers > LEARN MORE
ROBOTICS
Robotics Manufacturers
Denso RoboticsOmron AdeptPiabRobotiqUniversal RobotsYaskawa Motoman Industrial RobotsZimmer
Robotics Products
4-Axis SCARA Robots5- and 6-Axis RobotsCartesian RobotsCollaborative RobotsEnd of Arm ToolingMobile RoboticsUR Robot Pedestal
FEATURING: Universal Robots New e-Series > LEARN MORE
SERVICES & SOLUTIONS
Automation & Motion Control ServicesIndustrial NetworkingIndustrial ComputingRobotics Services & SolutionsSubassemblies
Industries
AutomotiveFactory AutomationFood and BeverageIntelligent TransportationMedicalPackagingPower GenerationRenewable EnergySemiconductor
INFO CENTER
Line CardFree Smart Motion Cheat Sheet
ABOUT MSI Tec
NewsVideos
Classes & Webinars
Moxa Cybersecurity Webinar Series
CONTACT US
Contact Us FormRequest a QuoteRMA RequestRequest LiteratureGeneral Terms
SEARCH
Search for:
Search
Search
Search for:
Search
Home Terms and Conditions
Terms and Conditions
PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE. All users of this site agree that access to and use of this site are subject to the following terms and conditions and other applicable law. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use this site.
Copyright
The entire content included in this site, including but not limited to text, graphics or code is copyrighted as a collective work under the United States and other copyright laws, and is the property of MSI Tec. The collective work includes works that are licensed to MSI Tec. Copyright 2017, MSI Tec ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. Permission is granted to electronically copy and print hard copy portions of this site for the sole purpose of placing an order with MSI Tec or purchasing MSI Tec products. You may display and, subject to any expressly stated restrictions or limitations relating to specific material, download or print portions of the material from the different areas of the site solely for your own non-commercial use, or to place an order with MSI Tec or to purchase MSI Tec products. Any other use, including but not limited to the reproduction, distribution, display or transmission of the content of this site is strictly prohibited, unless authorized by MSI Tec. You further agree not to change or delete any proprietary notices from materials downloaded from the site.
Trademarks
All trademarks, service marks and trade names of MSI Tec used in the site are trademarks or registered trademarks of MSI Tec
Warranty Disclaimer
This site and the materials and products on this site are provided “as is” and without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied. To the fullest extent permissible pursuant to applicable law, MSI Tec disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement. MSI Tec does not represent or warrant that the functions contained in the site will be uninterrupted or error-free, that the defects will be corrected, or that this site or the server that makes the site available are free of viruses or other harmful components. MSI Tec does not make any warrantees or representations regarding the use of the materials in this site in terms of their correctness, accuracy, adequacy, usefulness, timeliness, reliability or otherwise. Some states do not permit limitations or exclusions on warranties, so the above limitations may not apply to you.
Limitation of Liability
MSI Tec shall not be liable for any special or consequential damages that result from the use of, or the inability to use, the materials on this site or the performance of the products, even if MSI Tec has been advised of the possibility of such damages. Applicable law may not allow the limitation of exclusion of liability or incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you.
Typographical Errors
In the event that a MSI Tec product is mistakenly listed at an incorrect price, MSI Tec reserves the right to refuse or cancel any orders placed for product listed at the incorrect price. MSI Tec reserves the right to refuse or cancel any such orders whether or not the order has been confirmed and your credit card charged. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your order is cancelled, MSI Tec shall issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the incorrect price.
Term; Termination
These terms and conditions are applicable to you upon your accessing the site and/or completing the registration or shopping process. These terms and conditions, or any part of them, may be terminated by MSI Tec without notice at any time, for any reason. The provisions relating to Copyrights, Trademark, Disclaimer, Limitation of Liability, Indemnification and Miscellaneous, shall survive any termination.
Notice
MSI Tec may deliver notice to you by means of e-mail, a general notice on the site, or by other reliable method to the address you have provided to MSI Tec.
Miscellaneous
Your use of this site shall be governed in all respects by the laws of the state of California, U.S.A., without regard to choice of law provisions, and not by the 1980 U.N. Convention on contracts for the international sale of goods. You agree that jurisdiction over and venue in any legal proceeding directly or indirectly arising out of or relating to this site (including but not limited to the purchase of MSI Tec products) shall be in the state or federal courts located in Los Angeles County, California. Any cause of action or claim you may have with respect to the site (including but not limited to the purchase of MSI Tec products) must be commenced within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arises. MSI Tec’s failure to insist upon or enforce strict performance of any provision of these terms and conditions shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. Neither the course of conduct between the parties nor trade practice shall act to modify any of these terms and conditions. MSI Tec may assign its rights and duties under this Agreement to any party at any time without notice to you.
Use of Site
Harassment in any manner or form on the site, including via e-mail, chat, or by use of obscene or abusive language, is strictly forbidden. Impersonation of others, including a MSI Tec or other licensed employee, host, or representative, as well as other members or visitors on the site is prohibited. You may not upload to, distribute, or otherwise publish through the site any content which is libelous, defamatory, obscene, threatening, invasive of privacy or publicity rights, abusive, illegal, or otherwise objectionable which may constitute or encourage a criminal offense, violate the rights of any party or which may otherwise give rise to liability or violate any law. You may not upload commercial content on the site or use the site to solicit others to join or become members of any other commercial online service or other organization.
Participation Disclaimer
MSI Tec does not and cannot review all communications and materials posted to or created by users accessing the site, and is not in any manner responsible for the content of these communications and materials. You acknowledge that by providing you with the ability to view and distribute user-generated content on the site, MSI Tec is merely acting as a passive conduit for such distribution and is not undertaking any obligation or liability relating to any contents or activities on the site. However, MSI Tec reserves the right to block or remove communications or materials that it determines to be (a) abusive, defamatory, or obscene, (b) fraudulent, deceptive, or misleading, (c) in violation of a copyright, trademark or; other intellectual property right of another or (d) offensive or otherwise unacceptable to MSI Tec in its sole discretion.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless MSI Tec, its officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors and suppliers (collectively the “Service Providers”) from and against all losses, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, resulting from any violation of these terms and conditions or any activity related to your account (including negligent or wrongful conduct) by you or any other person accessing the site using your Internet account.
Third-Party Links
In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, MSI Tec may link to sites operated by third parties. However, even if the third party is affiliated with MSI Tec, MSI Tec has no control over these linked sites, all of which have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of MSI Tec. These linked sites are only for your convenience and therefore you access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, MSI Tec seeks to protect the integrity of its web site and the links placed upon it and therefore requests any feedback on not only its own site, but for sites it links to as well (including if a specific link does not work).
PRIVACY NOTICE.
This Privacy Notice applies only to information MSI TEC collects through the Website. MSI TEC is free to collect, retain and use such information as it deems appropriate. We will not disclose the name of the party contacting Us or providing such information without advance permission or as required by law. We take every precaution to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
COOKIES. We may analyze the information derived from cookies or other technology markers and match this information with data provided by a user or another party. Cookies track and target the interests of our users to improve the user experience on our site as well as identify repeat visitors to our site. You may be able to control or delete cookies through the Internet browser or other programs. Please note, however, that some parts of the Website may not function properly or be available if You refuse to accept a cookie or choose to disable the acceptance of cookies.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
This Privacy Notice and the Website may be updated, revised or modified from time to time. All such
updates, revisions or modifications will be effective when published by Us. By using the Website after modifications to the Privacy Notice, You will have confirmed Your assent to and acceptance of the modifications. If You object to any subsequent revision to the Privacy Notice, You must immediately discontinue use of the Website.
Call Us
(866) 397-7388
Contact Us
Request Quote
Shop Online
Colorado office (HQ) 8925 E. Nichols Ave. Centennial, CO 80112
Phone: (720) 875-9835
Email Us
©2020, MSI Tec, Inc. All Rights Reserved | Terms and Privacy Policy
Get in Touch!
(866) 397-7388
Follow Us!
